Guide to the Association of Class Officers, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Association of Class Officers, Yale University, records
1902-1963
RU 596
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
5.75
The records consist of correspondence, minutes, articles, notes, and financial records documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Association of Class Officers.
Yale University. Association of Class Officers
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 8-C-1 (YRG 8-C-1), Records of organizations open to all Yale alumni.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by record type.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, minutes, articles, notes, and financial records documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Association of Class Officers.
Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University -- Alumnae and alumnae -- Societies, etc.; Yale University. Association of Class Officers; Yale University. Yale Association of Class Secretaries
- Corrspondence, 1902-1963; Accession 1965-A-005
  - Correspondence with articles & miscellaneous notes
    - 1902-1919 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 2)
    - 1902-1928 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1919-1925 (Box 1, Folder 4 - 5)
    - 1922-1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1926-1942 (Box 1, Folder 7 - 11)
    - 1931-1941 (Box 1, Folder 12 - 17)
    - 1939-1942 (Box 1, Folder 18 - 20)
    - 1941-1943 (Box 1, Folder 21 - 22)
    - 1942-1950 (Box 2, Folder 23 - 25)
    - 1943-1949 (Box 2, Folder 26 - 34)
    - 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 35 - 39)
    - 1947-1949 (Box 2, Folder 40 - 45)
    - 1949 Jan-Dec (Box 2, Folder 46 - 49)
    - 1950 (Box 3, Folder 50 - 51)
    - 1950 Jan-Dec (Box 3, Folder 52 - 53)
    - 1950-1961 (Box 3, Folder 54 - 75)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 76 - 80)
  - Minutes of Annual Business Meeting, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Meetings
    - 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - 1943-1951 (Box 4, Folder 83 - 89)
    - 1955-1958 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - 1955-1960 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Minutes & Notices of the Yale Association of Class Secretaries, Publication Committee of the University Council, Executive Committee of the Alumni Board, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Annual Dinners
    - 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 93 - 94)
    - 1950-1958 (Box 4, Folder 95 - 103)
    - 1959 Convocation & Dinner (Box 4, Folder 104 - 105)
    - 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 106 - 110)
  - Clarence Day Memorial, 1936-1938 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Alumni Board, J. E. Lowes, 1940-1943 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Committee on Yale Alumni War Activities, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Alumni Survey
    - Correspondence, preliminary drafts, etc., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Letters from recipients of survey, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Report of Committee on the Organization of a Yale Class to the Executive Committee, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Statements & dues
    - 1951-1958 (Box 5, Folder 117 - 118)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 5, Folder 119 - 121)
  - Bills paid, 1952-1956 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Questionnaires, Class of '81-Class of '02S, [1956?] (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Letters from Class Secretaries & Treasurers, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - The Yale Class-A Guide for Class Officers, 1962
    - Copy for Class Officers booklet (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - Preliminary Draft (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - Revised copies (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Printed copies (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Article on Nuclear Research, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Yale Class Organization, Services available to Class Officers, undated (Box 6, Folder 130)